<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SafeCampus</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">MapsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_user_tracking_location">UserTrackingLocation</string>
    <!--    <string name="guide_book">10 Campus Safety Tips You Should Follow-->
    When large groups of people gather in one location, criminal activity can occur. Practicing
    campus safety measures, including safe college partying practices, can help reduce risks and
    minimize negative outcomes.

    Here are some essential campus safety tips to help you stay safe while still having fun:

    1.Know Your Way Around Campus: Consider downloading a campus map and get to know your way around
    the school during the day when students and faculty fill the campus.
    2.Use Locks: Always lock your dorm room or apartment door. This major deterrent can stop thieves
    in their tracks. Also, lock your car doors (even when driving) and keep valuables out of sight.
    3.Never Walk Alone After Dark: Always use the buddy system when walking at night. Most schools
    also offer a campus escort shuttle.
    4.Know Where the Emergency Systems Are on Campus: Scout out the emergency blue light phones so
    you know their locations. If you forgot your phone or have a dead battery, you can use these
    phones to contact the public safety office directly.
    5.Consider Carrying a Whistle, Pepper Spray, or Alarm: Any type of personal defense option, such
    as pepper spray or a whistle, may help stop an attack or alert a bystander that you're in
    trouble.
    6.Take a Self-Defense Class: Knowing specific self-defense tactics can increase the odds of
    fending off an attacker. Many schools offer these classes for credit or for free.
    7.Take Advantage of Campus Escort Services: Most schools offer campus escort services,
    particularly at night. Call the public safety office for contact information and hours of
    operation.
    8.Be Aware of Your Social Media Settings: Check your social media settings and make sure only
    friends can see your posts. Also, disable location finders on social media sites that publicly
    share this information.
    9.Avoid Drinking Too Much: Drinking to excess can result in bad choices that put you in
    difficult and dangerous situations. If you do plan on drinking, never accept a drink poured by
    someone you don't trust.
    10.Always Have Emergency Contacts in Your Phone: Make sure to input emergency contacts, such as
    the campus safety office, into your phone so you don't need to look them up in an emergency.


    <!--    </string>-->
</resources>